Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  - Unknown
    - Learn Swedish, 1978; TR-15602; Hildeman; Beite (Box 85)
      LRC #: SW 5
    - Learn Swedish, 1978; TR-15603; Hildeman; Beite (Box 85)
      LRC #: SW 6
    - Swedish Dialogues, 1987; TR-15604; Trancik, L. (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWD 1
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15605; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 1
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15606; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 2
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15607; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 3
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15608; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 4
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15609; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 5
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15610; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 6
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15611; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 7
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15612; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 8
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15613; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 9
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15614; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 10
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15615; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 11
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15616; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 12
    - Svenska for er, 1978; TR-15617; Higelin; Sveriges Radios forlag (Box 85)
      LRC #: SWE 13
    - Swedish: An Elementary Grammar Reader, 1985; TR-15618; Hird, Gladys et al (Box 85)
    - Swedish: An Elementary Grammar Reader, 1985; TR-15619; Hird, Gladys et al (Box 85)
    - Swedish: An Elementary Grammar Reader, 1985; TR-15620; Hird, Gladys et al (Box 85)
    - Swedish: An Elementary Grammar Reader, 1985; TR-15621; Hird, Gladys et al (Box 85)
    - Swedish: An Elementary Grammar Reader, 1985; TR-15622; Hird, Gladys et al (Box 85)
    - Swedish: An Elementary Grammar Reader, 1985; TR-15623; Hird, Gladys et al (Box 85)
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15624; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 1
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15625; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 2
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15626; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 3
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15627; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 4
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15628; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 5
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15629; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 6
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15630; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 7
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15631; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 8
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15632; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 9
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15633; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 10
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15634; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 11
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15635; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 12
    - Buntus Cainte, Undated; TR-15636; Domhnallain, Tomas O.; Oifig an Tsolathair (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRB 13
    - Progress in Irish, Undated; TR-15637; Government of Ireland (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRE 1
    - Progress in Irish, Undated; TR-15638; Government of Ireland (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRE 2
    - Progress in Irish, Undated; TR-15639; Government of Ireland (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRE 3
    - Progress in Irish, Undated; TR-15640; Government of Ireland (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRE 4
    - Progress in Irish, Undated; TR-15641; Government of Ireland (Box 86)
      LRC #: IRE 5
    - Spoken Russian - Holt Tapes, Undated; TR-15642; Leed, R. L. (Box 86)
      LRC #: RH 1
    - Spoken Russian - Holt Tapes, Undated; TR-15643; Leed, R. L. (Box 86)
      LRC #: RH 2
    - Spoken Russian - Holt Tapes, Undated; TR-15644; Leed, R. L. (Box 86)
      LRC #: RH 3
    - Spoken Russian - Holt Tapes, Undated; TR-15645; Leed, R. L. (Box 86)
      LRC #: RH 4
    - A Course in Modern Icelandic, 1984; TR-15646; Friejonsson, Jon (Box 86)
      LRC #: ICM 1
    - Samples of Languages: Icelandic and Vietnamese, Undated; TR-15647 (Box 86)
      LRC #: ZLM 3
    - Readings in Old Icelandic, Undated; TR-15648; Gordon, E. V. (Box 86)
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15649 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 1
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15650 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 2
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15651 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 3
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15652 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 4
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15653 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 5
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15654 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 6
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15655 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 7
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15656 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 8
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15657 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 9
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15658 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 10
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15659 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 11
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15660 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 12
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15661 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 13
    - Icelandic, Undated; TR-15662 (Box 86)
      LRC #: IC 14
    - Colloquial Sinhalese Lesson 36, 1986-07-01; TR-15663; Fairbanks, Gair; De Silva; South Asia Program (Box 86)
      LRC #: SNC 36
    - Accent Interview, Undated; TR-15664 (Box 86)
      LRC #: OB
    - Papiamentu - Stories, Proverbs, Dialogue, etc., 1971; TR-15665; Agard, F. B.; Cornell DMLL (Box 86)
      LRC #: Agard
    - Papiamentu, 1971; TR-16023; Agard, F. B.; Cornell DMLL (Box 86)
      Includes handwritten information sheet in box
    - Unknown, Undated; TR-16024 (Box 86)
      LRC #: A 2672
    - Xmas Eve at our house, 1959-12-24; TR-16025 (Box 86)
      LRC #: A 2007
    - Unknown masters on hubs, Undated; TR-16026 (Box 87)
    - Unknown masters on hubs, Undated; TR-16027 (Box 88)